<Document>
  # Welcome to the Aurum Sector.

  Until only fifty years ago, this unnamed sector was considered a mineral-rich, if dangerous, region of space.
  It is notorious for its ancient automated defence system still holding vigil in this otherwise empty corner of the galaxy.

  Besides the automated defence systems which roam and (mostly) just pester ships in their space, reports of hateful drones attacking any ship in sight still haunts the sector, which made travel here unappealing to the general public.

  The Sector is host to a variety of factions, many having fought in The Corporate War.

  It was a conflict which shook multiple neighbouring sectors, and for our story, left many great corporations such as NanoTrasen and Cybersun in a state of great disrepair and barely recognizable from what they were before.

  Long after The Corporate War, around the year 2270-2290, explorers discovered an abandoned laboratory station with the branding of Cybersun Industries.

  Inside a failing, spherical containment unit were "the remains of a dying star". Said to be so radioactive and full of energy, it burned the containment unit's outer layer into hot sludge as it leaked from it.

  This material was soon named Aurum by the exploration team that found it, starting a new gold rush. This corner of the galaxy became known as The Aurum Sector, different factions were pushed towards the common goal of recovering their former glory through this new substance, while privateers and spacers flock towards the promise of generational wealth.


  # Today is the year 2328.
  # And you are one of these spacers.

 While the sector is considered largely lawless, informally, representatives from each remaining faction have come together to organize "High Command", an entity with the intent to help fund public interests and steer sector development projects.

 While the factions often squabble, as High Command they form a united front against outside threats like foreign corpos or automated defense system raids.

</Document>
